https://www.maree-medical.com/content/30-privacy-policy

Home
Privacy-policy
Category
Incontinence Productsintocare Anti-Strip Jumpsuitsintocare Onesies/BodiesSuprima Anti-Strip JumpsuitsSuprima Onesies/BodiesAnti-Tear Jumpsuit/OnesieIncontinence SwimwearSpecial GlovesSafe-HipsSafety BlanketsAichner Anti-Strip SuitsAnti - DecubitusBips and Aprons
info
info
Shipping
Paying-Methods
Contact
Size-charts
FAQ
Links & info
Safe Buying
Shipped in Unmarked Boxes
Easy Payment Options
Privacy policyVersion 0.1- On 5-5-2018 this page has been updated.We are aware that you trust us. It is our responsibility to protect your privacy. On this page you can read which data we collect when you visit our website, why we collect these data and how we improve your experience using our website based on these data. So you will understand how we work.This privacy policy applies to the services o . You must know that https://www.maree-medical.com is not responsible for the privacy policy of other websites and other sources. By using our website you acknowledge to accept our privacy policy. https://www.maree-medical.com respects the privacy of all the visitors/users of its website and ensures that all personal information which you will give us, will be dealt with in a strict confidential manner. How we use the collected dataOur ServicesWhen you order one of our services/products then we will ask for personal data like name, birthdate etc. These data will be used to execute your order. These data will be stored on a security server owned by https://www.maree-medical.com or by a third party. We will not combine your personal data with other data. CommunicationWhen you send emails or other messages to us it will be possible that we will save these messages. Sometimes we will ask for your personal data when this is relevant. This enables us to answer your questions and requests. These data will be stored on a security server owned by https://www.maree-medical.com or by a third party. We will not combine your personal data with other data. CookiesWe collect data for research to get a better insight in our clients in order to tailor our services/products.This websites uses cookies. A cookie is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored in a user’s web browser while the user is browsing the website. Every time the user loads the website, the browser sends the cookie back to the server to notify the website of the user’s previous activity. This information gathered by the cookie will be stored on the security server of https://www.maree-medical.com or by a third party. We use this information to see how you use the website and to make reports on website activity in order to offer you other services and products related to your activity on internet.PurposeWe collect and use this information for no other purposes than described in our private policy unless we have received your permission to do otherwise. Third PartiesWe will not provide your data to other parties. In some cases your data will be shared internally but our personnel signed a non disclosure contract to respect the confidentiality of your personal data. AlterationsThis privacy policy is tuned to the current status of our website. Adjustments or changes on our website can lead to changes in the privacy policy. So we advise you to read our privacy policy on a regular basis. Personal Data OptionsWe offer all visitors the possibility to look at, to change or to delete all personal data which has been provided to us.Adjustments and termination/removal of NewsletterAt the bottom of all our mails you will find the possibility to adjust your personal data or to terminate the newsletter.Adjustments/Removal communicationIf you would like to alter your personal data or to remove these from our files then you can contact us. See below for contact information.Switch off cookiesMost browsers are set up to accept cookies but you can set up your browser to refuse cookies or to notify you when a cookie is being sent to you. It is however possible that some services and functions on our website and on other website do not function properly when you have switched off cookies on your browser.Questions and FeedbackWe check on a regular basis if we comply with the privacy policy.  If you have questions about our privacy policy do contact us:R. de RuijterEkkersrijt  13335692 AJ  SonThe NetherlandsVisitors only by appointmentPhonenumber: 0031 – 411 - 611369E-mail: info@maree.nlChamber of commerce number: 17129674VAT identification number: NL811640498B01
© 2020 - Maree Medical
